

CONTACT

3

+91 9636447793

52



savanyadav377@gmail.com



Vill. Bhojayara Th. Chaksu Dist. Jaipur (Raj) Rajasthan - 303903

SKILLS

- PHOTOSHOP
- FIGMA
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- BOOTSTRAP
- TAILWIND
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- DESIGN THINKING

EDUCATION

MASTER OF ARTS
 University of Rajasthan Jaipur

2021-2022

HOBBY

- VOLLEYBALL
- FARMING



https://github.com/raosavan96



https://www.linkedin.com/in/savanyadav-47607a272/

SAWAN KUMAR YADAV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

A professional web designer with 12 Month experience in website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. I can build valuable user interface and user experience for clients using my new skills and experience in web design. I want to create engaging, highly interactive web design for the future of the web.

EXPERIENCE

DVG Soft

Jun 2023 - Jun 2024

 Modifying and making changes according to client's requirements.
Making the website responsive.

GRRAS SOLUTIONS PVT. LTD

Jun 2024 - Present

Currently I am learning MERN stack at grras solutions pvt. ltd.

PROJECT

- https://dvgsoft.com/
- https://infogear.co.tz/
- https://weather-info-git-master-sawan-s-projects.vercel.app/
- https://todo-git-main-sawan-s-projects.vercel.app/